# TOMMELLOUL

## **ABOUT**

A multidisciplinary architect specializing in parametric design, with a vast experience in business intelligence, programming, music and visual arts. A firm believer in exploring and combining a wide array of practices, specifically within the intersection of art and technology.

## **GENERAL**

**BORN** 1987, Tel Aviv, Israel. **NATIONALITY** Israeli, French.

**PLACES LIVED 2013 - Present** Tel Aviv, Israel.

2012 - 2013 Paris, France.

2009 - 2012 Rotterdam, Netherlands.

## **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2019 **B.Arch in Architecture**, **Azrieli School of Architecture**, Tel Aviv University. 2001 - 2005 Major in Visual Arts, 'Thelma Yellin' High School of the Arts, Givatayim, Israel.

### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

**2016 - Present** BEA Architects & Town Planners, Junior Architect

> A member of the studio's creative design team. Currently leading 4 different projects in an array of scales. In charge of all technological aspects of the Studio

(Parametric design, Software purchasing & Integration).

2018 - 2019 **Lomdim**, Instructor & Coordinator

> Planned, coordinated and taught a course curriculum for Rhinoceros 3D, Cinema 4D, Grashopper for Beginners, Advanced Grasshopper and Python for designers.

2018 Bezalel Academy of Art and Design, Assitant Instructor

> Specialized in parametric design at PUL L Final Project studio unit, teaching 5th year students at the Department of Architecture of Bezalel while being a 4th year student in Tel Aviv University. Created in depth monthly tutorials and guided

students technically and conceptually alongside the studio's instructors.

2013 - 2016 Malam Team, BI Specialist

> Developed and maintained dashboards, reports, and dimensional data models for local and international clients. Planned data warehouses using ETL platforms and best practices to reflect corporate managerial reporting requirements. Created & customized tailor-made UX solutions for data visualization and report usability. Trained customers and employees in various aspects of business intelligence.

Tomba, Owner

2008 - 2013

World-renowned electronic music producer, 3 times in Beatport top 10 Dubstep Charts, over 1M views on Youtube and Spotify, and more than 25K fans on Facebook. World touring DJ with live performances in over than 30 cities in 3 continents. Hired a staff of three (booking agent, manager and accountant).

2007 - 2010 Datamine, Graphic Designer, BI Reporting Specialist

> Planned, Designed and Assimilated Cognos KPI and Cube systems Reporting for local and international clients. Developed customized & tailor-made UX solutions

for data visualization and report usability, using built-in methodologies.

2006 - 2008 Alphamale Primates, Co-founder

Organized & produced nightlife dance events in local clubs. Hired a staff of 4.

2006 - 2007 Marvad, Exam Scanner, QA Engineer

> Quickly advanced from an exam scanner to a QA engineer with no prior skills, education or experience.

## TOMMELLOUL

### **SKILLS**

CAD Rhinoceros 3D Expert

Cinema 4D Advanced 3ds Max Elementary Houdini Intermediate Revit Intermediate **Autocad** Advanced SketchUp Advanced CityEngine Elementary QGIS Expert

GIS QGIS Expert
CityEngine Elementary

SCRIPTING & VPL Grasshopper Expert

Dynamo Elementary

Touchdesigner Elementary **VVVV** Advanced **Processing** Intermediate Arduino IDE Advanced **Python** Elementary C/C++/C# Intermediate **HTML** Advanced **Javascript** Advanced Expert

CSS Expert
PL/SQL Advanced
G-code Elementary
Unreal Engine Intermediate

**GAME ENGINES** Unreal Engine Intermediate Unity Elementary

RENDERING Octane Advanced Lumion Expert

V-ray Advanced
Redshift Intermediate
Photoshop Advanced
Illustrator Advanced

Indesign Advanced
After Effects Expert

Premiere Intermediate
3D PRINTING Cura Advanced

Simplify3D Intermediate

SINGLE BOARDS Arduino Intermediate

Raspberry Pi Elementary

Cubase Expert

Abelton Live

LANGUAGES

**IMAGE & VIDEO** 

**EDITING** 

HebrewNative Speaker3D PrintingEnglishHighly FluentBasketballFrenchConversantAnimeDutchConversantTravelling

Advanced

**HOBBIES**